Rebecca Steele

Rehoboth, MA 02769 | Email: rsteele@rebeccasteele.net

SUMMARY

Technical writer with over 10 years of experience collaborating with subject matter experts, end users, and non-technical team members. Former IT systems administrator and technical support professional with diverse experience performing technical writing responsibilities within various IT support and systems administration roles.

SKILLS

- Markdown
- GitBook
- HTML5
- Content strategy
- CSS
- JavaScript
- C++
- Spotlight

- Git/GitHub
- Gimp
- Snaglt

- Visual Studio Code
- Slack
- Confluence

PROJECTS

Software user guide

https://docs.akoya.com/docs/data-recipient-hub-user-manual

While working at Akoya, I created (and currently maintain) a user manual for the company's developer portal, the *Data Recipient Hub*. This is a comprehensive guide that covers all the portal's functionality.

Project Highlights

- Intended audience: end users
- Reduced inbound support tickets and emails to account managers.
- Technologies used: Readme.io; Markdown

Nutanix CE Installation Guide

https://nutanix-deployment-guide.rebeccasteele.net/

A field installation guide for a fictitious Managed Services Provider (MSP) called RS Tech Services, this guide allows field engineers to perform initial deployments of Nutanix Community Edition at customer sites quickly and efficiently, necessitating fewer calls to senior technical personnel.

Project Highlights

- Intended audience: internal level 1 technical field staff
- Technologies used: GitBook, Microsoft Word, and Microsoft Excel

EXPERIENCE

Associate Technical Writer | Akoya, Boston, MA | Jan 2022 - Present

Develop external and internal technical documentation based on product updates or user feedback. Types of documentation include implementation guides, release notes, quick-starts, code samples, and diagrams.

- Developed a comprehensive user manual for Akoya's dev portal, the Data Recipient Hub, where little
 documentation previously existed. This document dramatically reduced repetitive support calls and
 inbound emails to account managers.
- Enhanced and fleshed out a user guide for an internal product's management console, which helped new employees learn the product more quickly.
- Completely reorganized the company's internal Confluence site to rectify content organization issues.

Systems Administrator | Rhode Island College, Providence, RI | June 2016 – Jan 2022

Managed and maintained a 400+ virtual Windows server environment, ensuring 99.9% uptime or better. Evaluated, monitored, and enhanced IT storage infrastructure with an emphasis on availability, reliability, scalability, security, data confidentiality, and system integrity.

- Directed the implementation of the Nutanix platform with AHV and produced all system documentation and as-builts. 0% downtime experienced with subsequent VM migrations.
- Created project implementation plan for Microsoft System Center Configuration Manager 2016 and directed project rollout, resulting in increased efficiency with client PC deployments.
- Improved efficiency of IT system and hardware deployments by producing internal-facing technical documentation by collaborating with vendor SMEs

Systems Administrator | Titan America, Norfolk, VA | Nov 2012 - June 2016

Provided tier 1 and 2 technical support and day-to-day administration and maintenance of key application systems, collaborating with vendors and other internal departments as required.

- Commended by CIO on writing skills and asked to write various "how to" articles and content for company intranet page
- Reduced call volume to the helpdesk by 10%+ by providing instruction and customer-facing documentation for commonly encountered issues
- Determined IT "problem areas" needing improvement in collaboration with department staff

ADDITIONAL IT EXPERIENCE

IT Helpdesk Analyst | American Eldercare, Delray Beach, FL | Feb 2009 - Apr 2012

EDUCATION

Fort Hays State University

B.S., Computer Science candidate

Roger Williams University

B.A., English

Community College of Rhode Island

A.S., Computer and Information Processing, programming concentration